naics.com 2019-05-04

# NAICS Association Privacy Policy | NAICS Association

EFFECTIVE MAY 25, 2018

NAICS Association, LLC is an information technology service provider. Headquartered in Rockaway, New Jersey, we provide Data solutions including Marketing List Procurement and Data Append Services.

NAICS Association, LLC respects the privacy of every individual who visits https://naics.com (“Website”) and/or purchases its Services. This Privacy Policy is our commitment to transparency in communicating how NAICS Association, LLC collects, uses, and discloses the information that is collected from you, the visitor of its website and/or customer as well as the choices you have with respect to the information.

**SCOPE OF POLICY**

This Privacy Policy applies to how we collect, use, and disclose information from the following individuals:  
• **Customers** – individuals who register, on their own or on behalf of an entity, to use NAICS Association, LLC Services with the creation or administration of a NAICS account.  
• **Marketing Participants** – individuals who provide their information to NAICS Association, LLC when they subscribe to marketing material.  
• **Website Visitors** – individuals who visit NAICS Association, LLC’s Website and opt to provide contact information including an email address to receive communications from NAICS Association, LLC.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to a Customer’s website. Our Customers are responsible for the information they or their end users store in their hosting environments as well as compliance with applicable laws and regulations, and NAICS Association, LLC’s terms related to the collection and storage or personal information.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Customers**

NAICS Association, LLC asks for your account information which includes your name, business name, email address, physical address, phone number, credit card and/or PayPal account information (stored directly with a third party processor), and website domain. By voluntarily providing NAICS Association, LLC with your account information, you represent that you own and consent to our use of such personal data.

**Marketing Participants**

NAICS Association, LLC may ask for your name, Company Name, email address, physical address, and phone number. Participation in events, surveys, contents, or subscribing to marketing material is voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this personal data.

**Website Visitors**

At your option, NAICS Association, LLC asks and may collect your name, email address, physical address, and phone number. In addition, we also collect information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, or other information as part of aggregated data.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

NAICS Association, LLC uses cookies and other tracking technologies to gather demographic information about you, identify your visits to our Website, other interactions with our Website, and personalize your search experience on our Website. We gather information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, browser type, date/time stamp, and store it in log files. To collect this information, a cookie, a standard feature of a website that allows us to store a small amount of data on your computer to allow our web servers to recognize you, may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Website. In some countries, including those in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the information in this paragraph may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

You can control how websites use cookies by changing your cookie settings (www.aboutcookies.org), but your modification may limit your use and functionality of some of the features on our Website. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies to provide you advertising based on your browsing activities. You may opt out of targeted advertisements by visiting http://optout.networkadvertising.org, or if located in the EEA, you may opt out by visiting http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/.

However, you can still place orders.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

NAICS Association, LLC uses the information it collects about you in the following ways:  
•To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support.  
•To contact you regarding any agreements or accepted terms that you may have with NAICS Association, LLC for the Services.  
•To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters. (Only if expressly requested by you)  
•To contact you regarding functionality changes to our Services or Website.  
•To develop new features and functionality to our Services and Website.  
•To collect payment and bill for our Services.  
•To help personalize searches.  
•To diagnose problems.  
•To find and prevent fraud.  
•To carry out other purposes as disclosed to you through the Website, or found in terms or an agreement between you and NAICS Association, LLC.  
•Process for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.

**HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION**

NAICS Association, LLC shares the information it collects about you in the following ways:  
• **Third Party Providers** – NAICS Association, LLC may share your information with third party providers that provide services on our behalf or resellers who provide NAICS Association, LLC Services. These companies may assist with marketing support, processing credit card payments, content delivery, email, providing sales leads, and customer support. Third party providers may only process personal information pursuant to NAICS Association, LLC’s instructions, and in compliance with the Privacy Policy and other applicable regulations (e.g. EU-US Privacy Shield framework).  
• **Advertising** – Based on the cookies and other tracking devices, we may work with advertising companies to display ads that may be of interest to you.  
• **Business Transactions** – To provide information to a third party in the event of any disposition of all or any portion of our business (e.g. reorganization, sale, assignment, bankruptcy).  
• **Aggregated or De-identified Data** – We may disclose or use aggregated or de-identified information with third party providers for research purposes relating to our Services.  
• **As Required by Law or Similar Investigations** – To comply with legal obligations (e.g. subpoena) or investigate potential legal violations. NAICS Association, LLC may be required to share personal data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and/or law enforcement requirements.  
• **Safety** – We may disclose your information to protect and defend the safety of NAICS Association, LLC in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.  
• **Consent** – NAICS Association, LLC may share your information with your consent.

**WHICH THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS DO WE SHARE DATA WITH**

**WooCommerce:**   Information submitted to us to Purchase Products and Services through our Site is stored in our Local systems. This information is used for the processing and managing of Orders, as well as Manage account settings.  If you signed up for an account, you can login and Access your information at NAICS.com/my-account.  You may also submit a request to have this information sent to you, or have it purged by emailing us at [Newsletter@naicsdata.com](mailto:Newsletter@naicsdata.com).

**Gravity Forms:**   Information submitted to us via our Forms is stored in our Local systems.  You agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy if you fill one of our Web forms.  You may submit a request to have your information sent to you, or have it purged by emailing us at [Newsletter@naicsdata.com](mailto:Newsletter@naicsdata.com).

**MailChimp:**   If you have opted to sign up for Alerts on Important News and Offers, your Data is stored with MailChimp as our marketing automation platform. By clicking to request Alerts in one of our forms, you also acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.  Information collected from forms is not sold or used by Third parties for their purposes; it is only used to provide you Email updates on our News and Offerings.

You can change your mind and unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at [newsletter@naicsdata.com](mailto:newsletter@naicsdata.com). We will treat your information with respect.

**Authorize.net:**   Information Related to Purchases made on our Site are stored in a PCI DSS compliant manner by Authorize.net.  This information is used for Accounting and Order Resolution purposes only. We will make an effort to only keep information deemed necessary to uphold Legal, Financial, and Contractual obligations.  You may submit Requests related to this information by emailing us at [orders@naics.com](mailto:orders@naics.com).

**PayPal:  ** Information Related to Purchases made on our Site are stored in a PCI DSS compliant manner by PayPal.  This information is used for Accounting and Order Resolution purposes only. We will make an effort to only keep information deemed necessary to uphold Legal, Financial, and Contractual obligations.  You may submit Requests related to this information by emailing us at [orders@naics.com](mailto:orders@naics.com).

**Google:** Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. You can use this link to download the Opt-out Browser Add-on: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  
Click here to opt-out of Google Analytics

**YOUR CHOICES**

You may unsubscribe from receiving promotional or marketing emails from NAICS Association, LLC at any time by using the “unsubscribe” link in the email received, or by emailing us at [newsletter@naicsdata.com](mailto:newsletter@naicsdata.com). As outlined in the Section, Cookies and other Tracking Technologies, you can also control your cookie settings.

With respect to your account information, you may update, correct or delete information that you provided to us by logging into your NAICS account or contacting us at [info@naics.com](mailto:info@naics.com).

**LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

For individuals in the EEA, NAICS Association, LLC ‘s legal basis for collecting and using your personal information will depend on the personal information collected and the specific context in which we collect it. NAICS Association, LLC will process personal information from you where, a) we have your consent to do so, b) where processing is necessary for NAICS Association, LLC to perform Services pursuant to an agreement, or c) where processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information, or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. At any time, you have the right to withdraw or decline consent. If you do not provide the requested information, NAICS Association, LLC will not be able to perform Services for you. Also, you have the right to object where we rely on our legitimate interests to process your personal information.

**DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS**

Individuals located in the EEA may have additional statutory rights available to them with respect to their personal information, including the right to access your personal information, have it erased, have it corrected, or object to or restrict processing. If you would like to make such a request, please email  [info@naics.com](mailto:info@naics.com) and we will respond within thirty (30) days. NAICS Association, LLC will need to verify that the individual is inquiring about his/her own information before we can assist with the request.

We will comply with such requests to the extent legally required by applicable law. For EU individuals, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.

**CHILDREN**

Our Website and/or Services is not directed at children and our services are designed for businesses. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age, and use of our services by children under 13 years of age is forbidden.

**CAN SPAM ACT**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:  
•Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders/services.  
•If you provide Informed Consent, we may also send you additional information about Business Updates, our Products, and Services.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:  
•NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
•Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
•Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
•Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
•Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
•Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICES**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via in-site notification within 72 Hours of Discovery of Breach.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CALIFIORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.  
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
•On our Privacy Policy Page

**Users are able to change their personal information:**  
•By emailing us  
•By calling us  
•By logging in to their account  
•By chatting with us or sending us a ticket

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

NAICS Association, LLC reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, however, should we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the changes, you may terminate your Services.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy, or wish to exercise any of your statutory rights, please contact us at:

NAICS Association, LLC  
Attn: Operations Manager  
129 Lakeshore Drive  
Rockaway, NJ 07866  
USA  
Email – [info@naics.com](mailto:info@naics.com)

**DISPUTES?**

The American Arbitration Association (AAA) is available to provide an independent recourse mechanism to resolve any disputes with NAICS Association regarding this privacy policy, and NAICS Association agrees to subject all such disputes to binding arbitration through that organization.Claims should be initiated through AAA,1101 Laural Oak Road,Voorhees, NJ,08043.For additional information on this process, call AAA at 1-877-495-4185 or by visiting the AAA website at http://www.adr.org. All AAA proceedings will take place in New Jersey or any other mutually agreed location.

On May 25th, 2018, we published a revised version of our Privacy Policy which includes our Cookie Policy. Your Continued use of NAICS.com means you agree to the revised Policies, so please take a few minutes to read and understand them.   
[Read our Privacy Policy](https://www.naics.com/privacypolicy)Agree Reject
